Patryk Kostek

(917) 348-8129 1996 8th st, Springfield, OR 97477 <u>kostek.patryk@gmail.com</u> www.linkedin.com/in/patryk-kostek

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic and quick-learning networking professional and student with 1~ year of experience as a Heldesk Technician at a Managed Service Provider servicing over 20 clients and 2,500~ endpoints as well as 3 years of front-facing customer service experience and 5 years of military service.

SKILLS

- System administration involving: Active Directory, O365, AzureAD, minor G-Suite
- Strong understanding of LAN and WAN technologies
- Business Continuity and Disaster Recovery and the management of snapshots and backups.
- Experienced with VPN (Virtual Private Network)
- Antivirus management and deployment. (ESET, SentinelOne)
- Understanding of VOIP technologies (3CX)

EDUCATION

• Lane Community College – Computer Network Operations AAS

Expected Graduation Date 2024

• 3CX Academy – Basic Certified Engineer

Awarded Date 03/10/22

• Fortinet NSE Training Institute – Network Security Associate (NSE 1, 2, 3)

Awarded Date 03/03/22

• The Datto Academy – RMM, Continuity, SaaS Protection

Awarded Date 02/25/22

EXPERIENCE

Help Desk Technician, Emerald Technology Group, Springfield, OR

February 2022 - September 2022

- Patching and general management of Windows servers using Datto RMM across over 20 clients.
- System administration to multiple clients under a managed service provider setting involving: Active Directory, O365, and G-Suite.
- Physical deployment of network equipment such as routers, firewalls, switches, and network racks.
- Providing hardware and software support, including backup software configuration.
- Experience with ESET and SentinelOne antivirus troubleshooting, resolution, and configuration.

Infantry Team Leader, US Marine Corps

June 2014 - June 2019

- Operated as the safety non-commissioned officer for 26 rifle ranges and coached 1,300 Marines with a 95% passing rate, 100% after requalification.
- Directly responsible for the health and well being of 12 different Marines as well as their mentorship under the Squad Leader and Team Leader role.

Barista/Cook, Odradeks Coffee House, Kew Gardens, NY

February 2014 - June 2014

- Managed store closing revenue in one of the highest volume Cafes in Kew Gardens, NY.
- Ensured proper inventory to execute peak rush hours efficiently and effectively.

Barista, Starbucks, Whitestone, NY

June 2013 - February 2014

- Ensured complete store adherence to the health, sanitation and safety guidelines given by the company.
- Gained front facing customer service experience in a high volume and stress environment